Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Rena Bartos Papers, 1960-1998 and undated, bulk 1975-1991
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials Series, 1977-1990 and undated, (3 boxes)
  - Originals (CLOSED)
    - Audio cassettes
      - OR9. Women Talk Business, 1990. Cassette. (Box 29)
      - OR10. Marketing to Women Around the World, 1989. Cassette. (Box 29)
  - Master copies (not for reference use)
    - Video materials (Box 30)
      Format: BetacamSP. Created: 2006.
      - MC1-MC6, MC8 (Box 30)
    - Audio materials
      Format: Audio cassette. Created: 2006.
      - MC9-MC10 (Box 30)
  - Use copies
    - Video materials (Box 31)
      Format: DVD. Created: 2006.
      - UC1-UC6, UC8 (Box 31)
    - Audio materials
      Format: Audio cassette. Created: 2006
      - UC9-UC10 (Box 31)
Indexes
Alphabetical List of Publications
Ads That Irritate May Erode Trust in Advertised Brands, 1981, Box 13
Beyond Derived Status, 1986 Box 14
Beyond the Cookie Cutters, 1981 Box 13
Challenging Our Assumptions, 1986 Box 14
Cinq tendences qui détermineront le marketing et la publicité dans les années 90, 1989 Box 14
Consumer View of Advertising--1974, 1975 Box 13
Exploring Mysterious Markets, 1979 Box 13
Founding Fathers of Advertising Research (with Arthur S. Pearson), 1977 Box 13
Founding Fathers of Advertising Research, 1986 Box 14
Future of the Advertising Agency Research Function, 1974 Box 13
How to Advertise to Women, 1995 Box 14
Insight on Selling the Working Woman, 1976 Box 13
International Advertising: Consumers, the Moving Target, 1984, Box 13
International Demographic Data? Incomparable! 1989 Box 14
Keeping Up With Changing Life Cycles, 1978 Box 13
Marketing Research: The Moving Target, 1976 Box 13
Moving Target, circa 1974 Box 13
Moving Target: Customer for Life Insurance, 1976 Box 13
Moving Target: The American Consumer 1970-1990, circa 1978, Box 13
Moving Target: The Impact of Women's Employment on Consumer Behavior, 1977 Box 13
New Woman, 1985 Box 14
Over 49: The Invisible Consumer Market, 1980, 1983 Box 13
Over 49: The Invisible Consumer Market, 1993 Box 14
Qualitative Research: What It Is and Where It Came From, 1985-1986 Box 14
Quiet Revolution, 1989 Box 14
Report of a Study Conducted on the Image of Women in Advertising, undated Box 13
Research, Creativity, and Tunnel Vision, undated Box 14
Target is Moving, 1975 Box 13
Target is Moving: The Changing Bank Customer, 1978 Box 13
Target: Latin America--The Changing Consumer Marketplace, undated Box 13
What About the Consumer Who Brushes His Teeth With Shampoo? 1984, Box 13
What Every Marketer Should Know About Women, 1978, 1983 Box 13
What Women Like, and Don't Like, In Ads, 1982 Box 13
Why Do You Work? 1979 Box 13
Women and Advertising, 1983 Box 13
Women and Travel, 1982 Box 13
Women As a Moving Target: Will It Continue? undated Box 14
Women: A Missed Mega Market? 1989 Box 14
Women's Forum, Inc.: The First 15 Years, 1990 Box 14
Alphabetical List of Speech Titles
Acceptance Speech, Market Research Council, 1989 Box 4
Advertisers and Consumers--New Perspectives, 1977 Box 1
Advertising and Credibility, 1984 Box 2
Advertising and Credibility, 1986 Box 3
Advertising and the Economy, 1975 Box 1
Advertising Research... What Should Be Measured? 1981 Box 1
Advertising: What...Why... How..., 1986 Box 3
Attitude of Mothers and Young Children Toward Toy Purchases and Toy TV Commercials, 1962 Box 1
Beyond the Cookie Cutter, 1984 Box 3
Beyond the Cookie Cutter, II, 1988 Box 4
Beyond the Rocking Chair, 1981 Box 1
Beyond the Rocking Chair, 1988 Box 4
Challenge of Change, 1986, 1988 Box 4
Challenging Our Assumption, 1986 Box 3
Challenging Our Assumptions About the Marketplace, 1990, 1992, Box 5
Changes and Challenges, 1985, 1986 Box 3
Changing Consumer Marketplace: Five Trends That Will Redefine Marketing and Advertising, 1987, 1988 Box 4
Consumer Behavior During Inflationary Times: Panel Discussion, 1981 Box 1
Consumer Profile of the 1980s, 1980 Box 1
Consumer Trends in the United States, 1989 Box 4
Customer for Life Insurance: A Moving Target, 1976 Box 1
Demographic and Social Trends in North America, 1990 Box 4
Demographics of Older Shoppers, 1982 Box 2
Do We Really Have to Make Them Mad to Sell Them? 1980 Box 1
Does Social Research Have Real Value in Marketing Decsions? 1982, Box 2
Effect of Changing Population Demographics on the Data Collection Profession, 1979 Box 1
Excellence in Advertising: Today and Tomorrow, 1984 Box 3
Exploration of Food Habits and Attitudes of Far Eastern Students, 1972 Box 1
Facts of Life, 1982, 1984 Box 2
Facts of Life: The Changing Consumer Marketplace, 1985 Box 3
Facts of Life: The Changing Consumer Marketplace, 1986, 1987, Box 4
Facts of Life: The Changing Supermarket Shopper, 1985 Box 3
Facts of Life: The Changing Supermarket Shopper, 1986 Box 4
Home Economics, 1977 Box 1
Honoring Women's Impact on the Economy: Yesterday and Today, 1998 Box 5
International Moving Target: The Changing Role of Women Around the World, 1987 Box 4
Keeping Pace with the Changing Women's Market Around the World, 1990 Box 4
Marketing Financial Services to Changing Customers, 1985 Box 3
Marketing the ERA, undated Box 5
Marketing to the Pacific Rim, 1985 Box 3
Marketing to Women Around the World, 1988-1990 Box 4
Marketing to Women in Canada and the United States, 1990 Box 4
Marketing Yourself, 1989 Box 4
Matrix Award Acceptance Speech, 1986 Box 3
Meeting the Cosmetic Needs of Tomorrow's Consumers: Changing Demographics and Changing Attitudes, 1983 Box 2
Moving Target, 1978-1980 Box 1
Moving Target, 1982-1983 Box 2
Moving Target: A New Look at the Consumer Marketplace, 1983, Box 2
Moving Target: A New Look at the Consumer Marketplace, 1984-1985, Box 3
Moving Target: Consumer Trends in the 1980s, 1983-1984 Box 2
Moving Target: The Changing Customer for Financial Services, 1985 Box 3
Moving Target: The Changing Women's Market, 1978 Box 1
Moving Target: The Changing Women's Market, 1982 Box 2
Moving Target: The Influence of Women's Employment on Consumer Behavior, 1977 Box 1
Moving Target: The Women's Car Market, 1987 Box 4
Moving Target: What Every Marketer Should Know About Women, 1989, Box 4
Moving Target--Changing Demographics--Changing Attitudes, 1983-1984 Box 2
Opportunites, 1982 Box 2
Opportunities and How to Capitalize on Them, 1976 Box 1
Over 49, 1984 Box 3
Over 49: The Invisible Consumer Market, 1986 Box 3
Overview: Setting the Context, 1989 Box 4
Perspectives on Women in Their Consuming Roles: The Moving Target, 1990 Box 4
Presentation of Market Research Hall of Fame to Henry Brenner, 1992 Box 5
Qualitative Research: What It Is and Where It Came From, 1985, Box 3
Reaching The Moving Target, 1992 Box 5
Reaching the Young Customer: A Strategy for Success in the Nineties, 1989 Box 4
Remarks at Memorial Service to Honor Dr. Ernest Dichter, 1992, Box 5
Research Creativity and Tunnel Vision, 1973 Box 1
Savings Market, undated Box 5
Seminar on Marketing to Women Around the World, 1989 Box 4
Social Change and the Travel Marketer, 1976 Box 1
Social Change Means New Marketing Opportunities, 1981 Box 1
Social Trends of the 80s, 1980 Box 1
Solving the Communications Puzzle, 1984 Box 2
Some Observations on Gender in Advertising, 1990 Box 4
Systems Approach to Research, 1964 Box 1
Target is Moving--The Changing Bank Customer, 1978 Box 1
Targeting the Top, 1984 Box 2
Trends in American Advertising, 1972 Box 1
Tribute to Ruth Whitney, 1993 Box 5
Use of Qualitative Evaluation: Problems, Pitfalls, and Potentials, 1983 Box 2
Use of the 1976 Survey of Income and Education, 1978 Box 1
Using Census Data, 1979 Box 1
Welcome from the Chairwoman, 1977 Box 1
Who Pipes, Who Pays, and Who Calls the Tune--The Agency Viewpoint, 1973 Box 1
Who Pipes, Who Pays, Who Calls the Tune? 1974 Box 1
Why a Full Service Industry? 1973 Box 1
Woman's Place (And Yours): A Changing Market, 1973 Box 1
Women as a Moving Target, 1978 Box 1
Women's Car Market: A Moving Target, 1990 Box 4
Working Woman Audience: The Moving Target, 1976 Box 1
Working Women: The Invisible Consumer Travel Market, 1973, Box 1